angry
腹白い
hey.
ね
The mask is too tight.
マ スクきつい
It's so tight I can't get it in.
きつくて入んないんだけど
Wow, that's amazing.
うわ、すごい
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
It doesn't hurt.
痛くない
It's really tough.
すーごいきついね
Good.
よいしょ
It happened like this
こうなっちゃって
good?
いい?
It's really tough.
す っごいきつい
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい
This feels so good.
これすげー気持ちいい
It's really tight.
めちゃくちゃ締まるね
It feels really good though.
す ーごい気持ちいいんだけど
What should I do?
どうしよう
terrible.
やばい
This is amazing.
すーごいこれ
Why is this so small?
なんでこんな、 なんかちっちゃいのこれ
terrible.
やばい
Is everyone in trouble?
みんなやばいの?
yeah?
ん?
Oku hit?
奥当たる?
It's true.
当たる
You look really comfortable.
すごい気持ちいい顔してるね
terrible.
やばい
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Maybe I should take a slightly different position.
ちょっと違う 体勢になっちゃおうかな
Have you ever ridden one?
乗 ったことある?
Yeah.
うん
Is there one?
あるの?
do not have.
ない
There is, right?
あるでしょ?
Amazing
す ーごい
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
wait a minute.
ちょっと 待って
Can you do that?
そんなことできるの?
amazing.
すごい
Sit back.
後ろに座って
Please stand up.
足立ててごらん
Please step in slowly.
ゆっくり足入れしてごらん
It feels good.
気持ちいいね
It feels so good.
すーごい気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
yes.
はい
Yeah.
うん
That's amazing.
すごいね
Awesome.
すーごい
It's closed.
閉 まるね
Can I take it out like this?
このまま出していい?
Is it okay?
いいの?
Take it out.
出して
Is it okay?
いいの?
I've stayed.
とどまってきちゃったね
Is it okay?
いいの?
Take it out.
出して
Do you want it out?
出してほしい?
Come in.
入ってごらん
Take it inside.
中に出して
I cum inside you.
中に出しちゃったよ
Is it okay?
いいの?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
It's a huge change.
すごい変わるね
When we first met.
最初に会ったときと
Yeah.
うん